<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".uı.skills.view.SkillsActivity">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="100dp"
            android:text="Skills"
            android:textSize="50sp"
            android:textColor="#787878"
            android:gravity="center"
            />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="370dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="I possess a diverse set of skills that make me a versatile and capable developer. My proficiency in Python extends to both scripting and application development, demonstrating my adaptability with this powerful programming language. Using Flask, I have successfully developed web applications and RESTful APIs, showcasing my expertise in this lightweight and flexible Python web framework. In the realm of web services, I am experienced in designing and implementing solutions that facilitate seamless communication between different software systems. My competency extends to mobile app development using Android Studio, where I create engaging and user-friendly applications tailored for the Android platform. Additionally, my Java programming skills are well-honed, allowing me to leverage its object-oriented features for the development of robust and scalable software solutions. In the domain of algorithms, I am proficient in designing and analyzing algorithms, demonstrating my ability to efficiently solve complex problems and optimize code for enhanced performance."
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:textAlignment="center"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            />

        <LinearLayout
            android:id="@+id/skillsLinearLayout"
            android:orientation="vertical"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">


        </LinearLayout>













    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>